[
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951b9c",
    "correctAnswer": "South Pole",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Peak of Mount Everest",
      "The Moon",
      "The Mariana Trench"
    ],
    "question": "In 1911 Roald Amundsen became the first person to reach where?",
    "tags": ["people", "firsts", "general_knowledge"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc8a",
    "correctAnswer": "Discombobulate",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Cacophony", "Dragoman", "Dragoman"],
    "question": "Which word is defined as 'to disconcert of confuse'?",
    "tags": ["words", "general_knowledge"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95045c",
    "correctAnswer": "7 Swans A Swimming",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "7 Maids a Milking",
      "7 Lords A Leaping",
      "7 Drummers Drumming"
    ],
    "question": "What did my true love give to me on the \"Seventh\" day of Christmas\"?",
    "tags": ["general_knowledge"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "6239f8199129041bf3925cc6",
    "correctAnswer": "Juliett",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Jump", "Jericho", "Jolly"],
    "question": "What word is used in the NATO Phonetic Alphabet for the letter J?",
    "tags": ["general_knowledge"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95032a",
    "correctAnswer": "Bonnie Parker",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Ma Baker", "Anne Bonny", "Mary Surratt"],
    "question": "Who was the first woman to be shot by the FBI?",
    "tags": ["general_knowledge"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fe32",
    "correctAnswer": "Euro",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Peso", "Lira", "Dollar"],
    "question": "What is the basic unit of currency for San Marino?",
    "tags": ["currency", "general_knowledge"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc98",
    "correctAnswer": "Argle-bargle",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Quomodocunquizing", "Valetudinarian", "Agastopia"],
    "question": "Which word is defined as 'copious but meaningless talk or writing'?",
    "tags": ["words", "general_knowledge"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "6239f82ca72e7a347ac879d3",
    "correctAnswer": "Quebec",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Queen", "Qualify", "Qwerty"],
    "question": "What word is used in the NATO Phonetic Alphabet for the letter Q?",
    "tags": ["general_knowledge"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951062",
    "correctAnswer": "Chihuahua",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Maltese", "Pomeranian", "Havanese"],
    "question": "What dog is named after a Mexican state?",
    "tags": ["animals", "central_america", "names", "general_knowledge"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc8b",
    "correctAnswer": "Doodle Sack",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Fipple", "Tittynope", "Quire"],
    "question": "Which word is defined as 'Old English word for bagpipe'?",
    "tags": ["words", "general_knowledge"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  }
]
